Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Local and Underground Press Serials TAM.758
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Local and Underground Press Serials
1871-2005
1970-1989
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
TAM.758
26 Linear Feet in 87 flat boxes and 10 manuscript boxes
The Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Local and Underground Press Serials contains roughly 600 titles published by local and underground presses in the United States, Europe, South America, Australia, and Canada. The collection dates between 1871 and 2005, with the bulk of the material dating from the 1960s through 1980s. The collection consists of serials published by local, independent presses, encompassing activist networks, local media companies, clubs, individuals, independent artist collectives and cooperatives, student groups, and local non-profits. Topics in the collection include local news, regional history, rural and urban community networks, community development, wages and employment, anarchism, socialism, communal and sustainable living, environmentalism, feminism, student activism, and local arts and media in the communities in which the serials were published.
Conditions Governing Access
Open to users without restriction.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This collection combines serials relating to Local and Underground Press drawn from two discrete groups of material held by the Tamiment Library. The first was a partially inventoried backlog of serials, received by the library through donations, subscriptions, and in archival collections. The second group consisted of around 1,700 serials, newspapers, and magazines, organized by title as an artificial collection, referred to as Periodicals.001 or Boxed Newspapers. This material was combined, inventoried, and arranged and described in subject-based categories in 2017. The accession number related to this collection is 2017.049.
Arrangement
Serials in this collection are arranged alphabetically by title.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Due to the fragile nature of certain original materials, researchers may be required to consult microfilm copies, preservation photocopies, or digital images of material in this collection.
Scope and Contents
The Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Local and Underground Press Serials contains roughly 600 titles published by local and underground presses in the United States (US), Canada, Europe, South America, and Australia. The collection dates between 1871 and 2005, with the bulk of the material dating from the 1960s through 1980s. The majority of the collection consists of incomplete runs of newspapers, magazines, newsletters, zines, comics, and bulletins published by local, independent presses in the US, encompassing activist networks, local media companies, clubs, individuals, independent artist collectives and cooperatives, student groups, and local non-profits. A significant quantity of the collection dates from the 1960s and 1980s, and documents feminism, environmentalism, peace activism, minority rights movements, and student organizing and the ways in which these movements affected discussions on the local level. Local presses from the Bay Area in California; Boston, Massachusetts; Chicago, Illinois; and New York, New York are well documented in this collection.
Among the topics addressed in the serials are local news, regional history, rural and urban community networks, community development, wages and employment, anarchism, socialism, communal and sustainable living, environmentalism, feminism, student activism, and local arts and media. They also include critiques of US foreign policy and mainstream media, and contain educational resources about international independence movements and solidarity. The vast majority of the collection originates in and documents the US, and include publications from regional political networks. A small amount of international publications are present in the collection and primarily consist of publications from Europe and Canada, with some publications from South America and Australia. No complete runs of publications are contained herein, and generally only a handful of issues of each publication are held.
Anarchism -- Periodicals.; Chicago (Ill.) -- Periodicals.; Women anarchists -- Political activity.; Community organization.; Serials (publications); Counterculture -- United States -- Newspapers.; Labor unions -- United States -- Newspapers.; Social movements -- United States -- Newspapers.; Underground newspapers -- United States; New York (N.Y.) -- Periodicals.; Boston (Mass.) -- Periodicals.; San Francisco Bay Area (Calif.) -- Periodicals.
- 19: Committee for Independent Political Action, New York, NY, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 1, Box 71)
- Acorn News: Arkansas Community Organizations for Reform Now, Little Rock, AR, 1977-1978 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Action Report: Come!Unity Press, New York, NY, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Acts Tracts & Facts: Angry Consumers and Taxpayers, Inc., Wharton, NJ, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Actuel!?: Jean-François Bizot, Paris, France, 1970-1971 (Box 92, Folder 1)
- ADA Review: Action in the Detroit Area, Detroit, MI, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Advocate: Vermont Low Income Advocacy Council, Montpelier, VT, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Agenda: Ann Arbor's Alternative News Monthly: Agenda Publications, Ann Arbor, MI, 1997 (Box 63, Folder 1)
- AKI Nueva York: Bloomington Independent Publishing Corp., New York, NY, 1955 (Box 69, Folder 1)
- Akron Beacon Journal: Beacon Journal Co., Akron, OH, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- All You Can Eat: All You Can Eat Collective, New Brunswick, NJ, 1970-1973 (Box 64, Folder 1-3)
- Alligator: American Liberation League, New York, NY, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Alternate Society: n.p., Toronto, Canada, 1971 (Box 92, Folder 2)
- Alternative: Naperville Central High School, Naperville, IL, 1970 (Box 46, Folder 19)
- Alternative Orange: Alternative Orange, Syracuse, NY, 1992 (Box 97, Folder 4)
- Alternative Press Digest: Alternative Press Digest, Kent, England, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Alternatives / 80's Coalition for a People's Alternative Newsletter: Coalition for a People's Alternative, New York, NY, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Amazing Grace: Florida Free Press, Talahassee, FL, 1970-1971 (Box 69, Folder 2)
- American Progress: American Progress Publishing Company, Meridian, MS, Undated (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Amityville Record: Amityville Publishing Co., Amityville, NY, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- An Introduction to NCLC: "The Word is Beware": Liberation News Service, New York, NY, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 1)
- Andromeda: Andromeda International, Inc., Stillwater, OK, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Ann Arbor Argus: White Panther Community News Service, Ann Arbor, MI, 1969-1971 (Box 64, Folder 4)
- Ann Arbor Sun: Rainbow People's Party, Ann Arbor, MI, 1971-1974 (Box 8, Folder 1-10)
- Aquarian: Aquarian Publishing Co., Montclair, NJ, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Archaeological Conservancy Newsletter: Archaeological Conservancy, Albuquerque, NM, 1994-1995 (Box 92, Folder 3)
- ARM: American Revolutionary Movement, Berkeley, CA, Undated (Box 69, Folder 3)
- Armed: n.p., circa 1970s (Box 92, Folder 4)
- Asheville Global Report: Asheville Global Report, Asheville, NC, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Asian New Yorker: Asian New Yorker, Rego Park, NY, 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 8, Box 21, Folder 1)
- ASP: Appalachian Student Press, Greenville, TN, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Aufbau: New World Club, Inc., New York, NY, 1944 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Augur: Augur Publishing Co., Eugene, Or, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Augusta Courier: The Courier Publishing Company, Augusta, GA, 1961-1965 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Austin Javelina: Austin Javelina, Austin, TX, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Avatar: Avatar, Inc., Boston, MA, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Avatar: Trust Inc., Boston, MA, 1967 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- B.A.D. (Boston After Dark): Y.M.I. Inc., Boston, MA, Undated (Box 60, Folder 2)
- Bad Newz: Bob Z / Sarris Bookmarketing, New York, NY, Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Baggage Underground: Radical Rock Movement, Osasco, Brazil, Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Baltimore Independent: Paine Pub. and Print. Co., Baltimore, Md, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Bandera Negra: Los Anarquistas de Peru, Lima, Peru, Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Barb on Strike: Red Mountain Tribe, Berkeley, CA, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Barbedwire: Barbedwire, Vancouver, BC, Canada, circa 1980s (Box 92, Folder 5)
- Basement Newsletter: Basement, New York, NY, Undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Bay Area Reporter: Bay Area Reporter, San Francisco, CA, 1978 (Box 71, Folder 2)
- Beacon Hill Update: State House Presence Project, Boston, MA, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Behind These Walls: Little Red Printhouse, Basking Ridge, NJ, 1979 (Box 75, Folder 3)
- Berkeley Tribe: Berkely Tribe, Berkeley, CA, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Berkeley Tribe: Red Mountain Tribe, Berkeley, CA, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Berkeley Tribe: Red Mountain Tribe, Berkeley, CA, 1969-1972 (Box 86, Folder 1-10, Box 87, Box 88, Folder 1-5)
- Birth of a Revolutionary Movement in Yugoslavia: Black & Red, Kalamazoo, MI, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Bitch Nation: Bitch Nation, New York, Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Black Liberator: Black Liberation Alliance, Chicago, IL, 1969-1970 (Box 69, Folder 4)
- Boll Weevil: University of Alabama, Tuscaloosa, AL, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Borrowed Times: Montana Reconnaissance Project Inc., Missoula, MT, 1974-1975 (Box 31, Folder 43102)
- Boston After Dark: Auburn Colony Press, Boston, MA, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Boston Phoenix: American Colony Press, Boston, MA, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Both Sides Now: Both Sides Now, Jacksonville, FL, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 17, Box 31, Folder 5)
- Bread, Peace, and Land: Independent Community Voice, Cleveland, OH, 1971-1972 (Box 64, Folder 5)
- Breaking the Ice: Breaking the Ice, Akron, OH, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 18, Box 63, Folder 4)
- Breitenbush Newsletter: Breitenbush Hot Springs Retreat and Conference Center, Detroit, OR, 1983 (Box 92, Folder 6)
- Brick: Brick, Russellville, AL, Undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Briefing: Seattle Consumer Action Network, Seattle, WA, 1984 (Box 92, Folder 7)
- Broadside and the Free Press: Broadside Publications, Cambridge, MA, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 5)
- Broadway Local: West Side Community Newspaper, New York, NY, 1971-1972 (Box 21, Folder 3-5, Box 96, Folder 7)
- Bronx County Historical Society Journal: Bronx County Historical Society, Incorporated, Bronx, NY, Undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Brooklyn World-Telegram: Brooklyn World Telegram, Brooklyn, NY, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Buffalo Courier-Express: Buffalo Courier-Express, Buffalo, NY, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Buffalo Insighter: Insighter, Buffalo, NY, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Buffalo Peace & Freedom House Organ: Buffalo P&F, Buffalo, NY, 1969 (Box 92, Folder 8)
- Buffalo Sun: Western New York Offset Press, Inc., Buffalo, NY, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Bullet: Mary Washington College, Fredericksburg, Virginia, 1970 (Box 64, Folder 6)
- Bureau of Public secrets: Bureau of Public Secrets, Berkeley, CA, Undated (Box 1, Folder 21, Box 71, Folder 3)
- Campus Review: Campus Review, Iowa City, IA, 1979-1993 (Box 6, Folder 5, Box 42, Folder 4)
- Canadian Free Press: Argyle Cooperative House, Ontario, Canada, circa 1970s (Box 97, Folder 13)
- Cascade Community News: Cascade Community Center and Council, Seattle, WA, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Catalogo: Edicoes Antigona, Lisbon, Portugal, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Centennial Post: The Washington Post / The Smithsonian Institution, Washington, DC, 1876 (Box 70, Folder 1)
- Chicago Express: Chicago Express, Chicago, IL, Undated (Box 72, Folder 1)
- Chicago Journal: The Chicago Journal, Chicago, IL, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Chicago Reporter: Chicago Reporter, Chicago, IL, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Chicago Reporter: Community Renewal Society, Chicago, IL, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Chicago Seed: Seed Publishing, Chicago, IL, Undated (Box 21, Folder 6-7, Box 42, Folder 11, Box 66, Folder 1, Box 94, Folder 2-5)
- Chico News & Review: Chico Community Pub., Inc., Chico, CA, 1978 (Box 68, Folder 1)
- Chinook: Chinook, Denver, CO, 1970-1971 (Box 69, Folder 6)
- Chronicle of the Historical Society of the Tarrytowns, Inc.: Historical Society of the Tarrytowns, Inc., Tarrytown, NY, 1990-1993 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Citizens Party Bulletin: King County Citizens Party, Seattle, WA, 1981-1982 (Box 92, Folder 9)
- Citizens Party Newsletter: Washington State Citizens Party, Seattle, WA, 1981 (Box 92, Folder 10)
- Citizens' Voice: Wilkes-Barre Council of Newspaper Unions, Inc., Wilkes-Barre, PA, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- citta futura: citta futura, Rome, Italy, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- City Record: City of New York, New York, NY, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- City Sun: City Sun Publishing Company, New York, NY, 1985-1988 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Clash: Newspaper of Resistance in Europe: Slagerzicht, Amsterdam, Netherlands, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Clinton St. Quarterly: Out of the Ashes Press, Portland, OR/Seattle, WA, 1987 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Cold Steel: Onondaga Publishing Co., Buffalo, NY, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Collective Endeavor: Women's Press Collective, Brooklyn, NY, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Collectors' Network: unknown, Stoughton, WI, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- College Press: The Press, New York, NY, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Collettivo CR: Collettivo, CR, Torino, Italy, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Columbus Free Press: Columbia Free Press, Columbus, OH, 1979-1987 (Box 10, Folder 36, Box 11, Folder 1-11, Box 13, Folder 4-7)
- Come Unity: Come Unity, St. Petersburg, FL, 1976-1987 (Box 1, Folder 30, Box 44, Folder 7, Box 63, Folder 5)
- Common Sense: People's Bicentennial Commission, Washington, DC, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 31-32, Box 6, Folder 7)
- Common Sense: Common Sense, Springfield, MA, 1969 (Box 71, Folder 9)
- Common Sense: Bloomington Independent Publishing Corp., Bloomington, IN, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 8-9)
- Community Control: Northside Campaign for Community Control, Chicago, IL, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Community Dispatch: St. Louis County Family Collaborative Services, Cherry, MN, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Community Memory News: Community Memory Project, Berkeley, CA, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Community News: Community News, Roxbury, MA, Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Community Press Features: Urban Planning Aid, Cambridge, MA, 1979-1983 (Box 68, Folder 2-3)
- Community Reporter: The Community Reporter, Detroit, MI, Undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Concubine: n.p., New York, NY, circa 1990s (Box 92, Folder 11)
- Connections: Connections, Inc., Madison, WI, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Connections Connections: Connections, Madison, WI, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Consumer Outlook: Seattle Consumer Action Network, Seattle, WA, 1983 (Box 92, Folder 12)
- Corpus Creator News: Sons of Light INC., New York, NY, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Cos Miximsoc: n.p., Amsterdam, Holland, circa 1980s (Box 92, Folder 13)
- Counter Information: independent collective, Edinburg, Scotland, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Country Journal: Country Journal, Plainfield, VT, 1974 (Box 96, Folder 4-6)
- Coyote: Southwest Alternatives Institute/COYOTE, Tuscon, AZ, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Crossbronx Express: The Bronx People, Bronx, NY, 1970 (Box 60, Folder 3)
- Crystal City News: Crystal City News, Bowling Green, OH, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- D.C. Gazette: D.C. Gazette, Washington, DC, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Daily Barbarian: Daily Barbarian, Detroit, MI, 1994 (Box 63, Folder 6)
- Daily Challenge: Thomas H. Watkins, Brooklyn, NY, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Daily Clarion: Daily Clarion, Toronto, Canada, 1922 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Daily Columbia Spectator: Spectator Publishing Co., Inc., New York, NY, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Daily Free Press: United Publishing, Inc., Boston, MA, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Daily Journal: F.W. Dodge Division McGraw-Hill Information Systems Company, Denver, CO, 1974 (Box 95, Folder 7)
- Daily Mirror: Daily Mirror, New York, NY, 1953 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Daily Noose: Noose Syndicate Co., Inc., New York, NY, Undated (Box 51, Folder 2)
- Daily Planet: Daily Planet, Chicago, IL, Undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Daily Rag: The Daily Rag, Washington, DC, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Dallas Notes/Hooka: Humanitarian Order of Kosmic Awareness, Dallas, TX, 1970-1972 (Box 61, Folder 3-8)
- Dark Night Field Notes: Dark Night Press, Chicago, IL, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Dawn: Independence Foundation, Inc., Portland, IN, 1957-1959 (Box 21, Folder 8-9)
- day break: Appleseed Press, New York, NY, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 8-9)
- DC Free Press: D.C. Independent Media Center, Washington, DC, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- DC Gazette: Capital East Gazette, Washington, DC, 1982-1983 (Box 44, Folder 9)
- De Kargadoor: n.p., Utrecht, Netherlands, 1971 (Box 92, Folder 14)
- de Media: de Media, Belgium, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- De Notenkraker: VOLK, Amsterdam, Netherlands, 1915 (Box 66, Folder 2)
- Delaware Alternative Press: Delaware Alternative Press, Wilmington, DE, 1981-1986 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Delaware Valley Socialist Voices: Delaware Valley Committee of Correspondence, Philadelphia, PA, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Der Lange Marsch: Sozialistisches Zentrum, Berlin, Germany, Undated (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Der Radikalismus Die Kinderkrankheit Im Kommunismus: Verlag JHW Dietz Nachf, Berlin, Germany, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Derelicked: Derelicked, Ravinia, IL, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Detroit: Detroit Free Press, Detroit, MI, 1967-1983 (Box 66, Folder 3)
- Detroit Free Press: Detroit Free Press, Inc., Detroit, MI, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Dialectic and History: An Introduction: Radical America, Cambridge, MA, Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
- DIALOGUES Boston: Gordon Brumm, Cambridge, MA, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Dillinger Relic: Arthur D. Hlavaty, Durham, NC, 1984 (Box 92, Folder 15)
- Directory of Progressive Organizations in Baltimore: Progressive Action Center, Baltimore, MD, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- DISorientation: Hermes / DISorientation Collective, San Francisco, CA, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Disorientation Manual: New Indicator Collective, San Diego, CA, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Distant Drummer: Tixeon Inc., Philadelphia, Pa., 1970 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Dock of the Bay: The Bay Area Media Network, San Francisco, CA, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 4-5)
- Done in Houston: Quixote Group, Houston, TX, 1979 (Box 92, Folder 16)
- Donnelly/Colt Progressive Resources Catalogue: Donnelly/Colt, Hampton, CT, 1995-1999 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Door: Door, San Diego, CA, 1971-1973 (Box 69, Folder 7)
- Drugs: Phoenix Press, Undated (Box 75, Folder 1)
- Druid Free Press: Druid Free Press, Tucson, AZ, 1970 (Box 69, Folder 8)
- Duck Power: GI's Against Fascism, San Diego, CA, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Earth Nation Sunrise: Church of the Earth Nation, Nashiville, IN, 1982-1983 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- East Boston Community News: East Boston Community Communications, Inc., Boston, MA, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Eastside Social Justice Reporter: Streetside Boosters, Springfield, IL, 1983 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Echo: Echo, Austin, TX, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Edge City: Edge City, Syracuse, N.Y., 1970 (Box 69, Folder 9)
- El Gallo: El Gallo News, Denver, CO, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- El Grito Del Norte: El Grito del Norte, Espanola, NM, 1968-1973 (Box 14, Folder 6-9)
- El Popo: California State University Northridge, Northridge, CA, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 2)
- El Popo: San Fernando Valley State College, Pacoima, CA, 1960-1999 (Box 63, Folder 3)
- El Provo: Periodico Alternativo Libertario: n.p., Barquisimeto, Venezuela, circa 1970s (Box 92, Folder 17)
- El Semanario Cordobles: Cordoba, Spain, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Eleftheria: Eleftheria, New York, NY, 1940 (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Encyclopédie des nuisances: dictionnaire de la déraison dans les arts, les sciences et les métiers: Francois Martin/mpressions F.L., Paris, France, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Enrage: Enrage, New York, NY, 1969 (Box 46, Folder 16)
- Erie Grassroots Newsletter: Silas Townsend, Erie, PA, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Europapers' Intertribal Magic Ink Express: Underground Press Syndicate, Zurich, Switzerland, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Every Other Weekly: Every Other Weekly, San Francisco, CA, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Every Other Weekly: Daily Californian, Berkeley, CA, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Everything for Everybody: Everything for Everybody, New York, N.Y., 1975-1977 (Box 70, Folder 2)
- Exit: HAPOTOC Social Improvement Project, Leeuwarden, Holland, 1978 (Box 75, Folder 4)
- Expose: Expose, New York, NY, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 3, Box 91, Folder 1)
- Extra!: Extra!, Providence, RI, 1968 (Box 60, Folder 4)
- Eye: Eye, Gainesville, FL, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Falling Apart: Falling Apart Inc., Bronx, NY, Undated (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Fast Fiddling: Penny Each Press, Thetford Hill, VT, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Federation: Central Seattle Community Council Federation, Seattle, WA, 1983-1985 (Box 6, Folder 13, Box 92, Folder 18)
- Fenway News: Volunteers of the Fenway Community, Boston, MA, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Fetish Speaks!: Black & Red, Detroit, MI, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Fire: Forces of Internationalist Revolutionary Energy, Chicago, IL, 1969 (Box 70, Folder 3)
- Fire!: Students for a Democratic Society (SDS), Chicago, IL, 1969 (Box 65, Folder 1)
- Firearms & Self-Defense: International Liberation School, Berkeley, CA, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Firing Line: Join Community Union and National Organizing Committee, Chicago, IL, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Five Borough Report: Five Borough Institute, New York, NY, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Focus on Boston: Boston Citizens for Participation Politics, Boston, MA, 1971 (Box 71, Folder 4)
- Foolkiller: Mountain View Folk University Society, Kansas City, KS, 1978-1979 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Forty Acres and a Mule: Educational Program of the New York Urban League, New York, NY, 1968 (Box 64, Folder 8)
- Forum: Fremont Public Association, Seattle, WA, 1984-1986 (Box 43, Folder 7-8)
- Foward Motion: Coalition, Storrs, CT, 1974 (Box 64, Folder 7)
- Fox Valley Kaleidescope: Liberation News Service and the Underground Press Service, Oshkosh, WI, 1970 (Box 70, Folder 4)
- Free Flowing: Free Flowing, Ames, IA, 1976 (Box 64, Folder 10)
- Free for All: Devestan Enterprises/Better World Educational Corporation, Madison, WI, 1973-1981 (Box 40, Folder 1-10, Box 41, Folder 4-8)
- Free Prairie Press: Free Prairie Press / "Published by people", Champaign, IL, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Free Press: The Free Press, Somerville, MA, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Free Press of Louisville: Freep Publishing Co., Louisville, KY, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Free Press Underground: Columbia Free Press Corp., Columbia, Mo., 1967 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Free Seed: SEED, Chicago, IL, Undated (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Free Spirit: Living Network Productions, Brooklyn, NY, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Free Student: Free Student, New York, NY, Undated (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Free Student: May 2nd Movement, New York, NY, 1964 (Box 66, Folder 4)
- Free the Genitals! Cage the Generals!: SMILE Magazine published by Schiz-Flux, Madison, WI, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Free Venice Beachhead: Beachhead Collective, Venice, CA, 1968-1974 (Box 26, Folder 9-11)
- Free Vermont: Red Clover Collective, Putney, VT, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Freedom News: Freedom News, Inc., Richmond, CA, 1969-1974 (Box 41, Folder 1-3, Box 62)
- Freeway: Freeway, Duluth, MN, Undated (Box 68, Folder 4)
- Fremont Forum: Fremont Public Association, Seattle, WA, 1983 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Frendz: Frendz, London, England, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Friends: TF Much Co Ltd., London, England, 1971 (Box 62, Folder 4)